princessauto.com 2009-12-06

# Privacy Policy

| 

We believe that all Princess Auto Ltd. customers should be treated fairly, honestly, and with respect. We value our relationship with our customers, and as such, Princess Auto Ltd. is committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, security and privacy of your information.

Our privacy policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it and how we use it at our retail locations, our National Call Centre, Home Office and at www.princessauto.com.

Princess Auto Ltd. DOES NOT sell any of your information to third parties.

When you contact our National Call Centre to place an order, we collect your name, mailing address, phone number and credit card information. 

How is this information used?

We use this information to process your order. We may also need to use your phone or fax number, email or mailing address to contact you if we have any questions about your order. We would also use this information to send you our promotional materials if you requested them. 

To learn more about our customers and improve our service to you, this information may be used for statistical purposes. All of the statistical information collected does not identify you personally and is used strictly for internal analysis purposes. The data is not shared with anyone outside of Princess Auto. 

Providing this information to us is optional.

Any purchases you make in-store will be tied to your account; this being the name, mailing information, phone number and email address you have provided to us. If you are making a return or exchange, and have misplaced your receipt, all we need to do is look up your information and the appropriate purchase in order to process the return or exchange. 

Every time you make a purchase, your information is updated on our database which we use to mail our flyers and catalogues from. For those of you who have opted to receive our promotional materials, this provides to you a quick and easy way to update your information to ensure you don't miss any of our promotional sale flyers and catalogues.

We may also use this information for statistical purposes to learn more about our customers and improve our services to you. All of the statistical information collected does not identify you personally and is used strictly for internal analysis purposes and is not shared with anyone.

For prepaid merchandise, we require identification of the person picking up the order. This information may be recorded, and retained, only as long as necessary to confirm customer receipt of their order. We do this to protect our customers and ourselves from fraud, and ask our customers to inform the people they have picking up the order that this will be required.

When paying by cheque, we require a driver's license and a credit card. 

When you make a purchase online at www.princessauto.com, we collect your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information. We use this information to process your order. If you have also requested that you would like to receive our promotional materials (flyer, catalogue or e-flyer), we use your name, address and email address (if applicable) to fulfill this request. We may also need to use your phone or fax number, email or mailing address to contact you if we have any questions about your order.

Princess Auto does not sell any of your personal information to anyone. We do contract to third parties to fulfill your order (courier service) and send you our promotional materials (mail service providers). We only share with these third parties the information required to fulfill these duties and do not authorize them to use your information in any other way. We have confidentiality agreements in place to ensure the protection of your personal information. 

We only want to send you our promotional materials if you want to receive them. If you prefer not to receive information from us about our products, services, contests, or promotions, please contact us:

By Mail: ATTN: Circulation, PO Box 1005, Winnipeg, MB R3C 2W7

By Phone: 1-800-665-8685

By Fax: 1-800-265-4212

By email: Send an email to [mailer@princessauto.com](mailto:mailer@princessauto.com) Subject: Remove

If you have any questions regarding this policy or the way we collect, use or disclose your personal information, please feel free to choose from one of the following options:

-Visit a store near you and speak with a Team Leader.

-Contact our Privacy Officer via email at privacy@princessauto.com, or by mail; Attn: Privacy Officer to Princess Auto, P.O. Box 1005, Winnipeg, MB R3C 2W7.

-Contact our National Call Centre at 1-800-665-8685.
